Guide to the Time Inc. Time-Life News Service Records 1935-1987 MS 3009-RG 14
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Staff Files, 1936-1987; 46.8 Linear feet in 49 record cartons
  - Subseries IV.A. General Files, 1936-1987; 26.6 Linear feet in 29 record cartons
    - Coggin, Dan, 1972 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 13)
    - Coggin, Dan [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Coghill, Carol, 1952-1957 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 14)
    - Cole, David, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 15)
    - Coleman, Joseph, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 16)
    - Coleman, Joseph [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Collier, Andrew, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 17)
    - Comstock, Craig K., 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 18)
    - Comstock, Craig K. [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Connery, Don, 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 19-21)
    - Connery, Don [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Constable, Anne, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 22-23)
    - Constable, Anne [RESTRICTED], 1975-1983 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Constable, Rosalind, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 24)
    - Conyers, Nathan, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 25)
    - Conyers, Nathan [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Cook, Jess Lee Jr., 1954-1960 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 26)
    - Cook, Jesse Lee Jr. [RESTRICTED], 1965-1977 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Cooke, Jerry, 1954-1960 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 27)
    - Cornwall, Barbara, 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 28)
    - Cory, Christopher, 1963-1975 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 1)
    - Cory, Christopher [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Coughlan, Robert, 1948-1961 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 2)
    - Coutu, Diane, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 3)
    - Coutu, Diane [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Cowan, L. Geoffrey, 1965 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 4)
    - Cowan, L. Geoffrey [RESTRICTED], 1963 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Crane, Ralph, 1951-1957 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 5)
    - Crawford, Bernadine [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Cray, Douglas, 1956-1964 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 6)
    - Cray, Douglas [RESTRICTED], 1959-1964 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Creed, John, 1976-1985 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 7)
    - Creed, John [RESTRICTED], 1977-1986 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Crocker, Alice, 1946-1949 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 8)
    - Cronin, Mary, 1975-1982 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 9)
    - Cronin, Mary [RESTRICTED], 1970-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Crutcher, Larry, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 10)
    - Crutcher, Larry [RESTRICTED], 1969-1971 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Culbert, Mike, 1961 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 11)
    - Cunningham, James, 1958 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 12)
    - Curtis, Sally Elizabeth [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Danforth, Kenneth C., 1965-1978 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 13-14)
    - Danforth, Kenneth C. [RESTRICTED], 1967-1970 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Dang, Nguyen Thuy, 1967 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 15)
    - Davidson, Ralph, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 16)
    - Davidson, Spencer, 1973 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Crane, 1971-1977 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 18)
    - Davis, Crane [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Davis, Crane: Memoranda, 1971 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 19)
    - Dawson, Robin Frost, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 20)
    - Dawson, Robin Frost [RESTRICTED], 1971-1973 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Demarest, Mike, 1958-1961, 1984 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 21)
    - DeVoss, David, 1970-1981 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 22-24)
    - DeVoss, David [RESTRICTED], 1971-1981 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Diederich, Bernard, 1957-1983 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 25-30)
    - Diederich, Bernard [RESTRICTED], 1963-1984 (Offsite-box R48)
    - DiFatta, Peter, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 31)
    - DiFatta, Peter [RESTRICTED], 1975-1983 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Dinan, Dennis, 1982 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 32)
    - Dobie, Beatrice, 1954-1960 (Offsite-box 3209, Folder 33)
    - Doerner, William, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 1)
    - Doerner, William [RESTRICTED], 1978-1984 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Dominis, John, 1946-1958 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 2)
    - Donovan, Hedley, 1959-1979, 1985 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 3-5)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Trip to Cairo and Moscow with Grunwald, 1969 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 6)
    - Dowd, Maureen, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 7)
    - Dowd, Maureen [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Downing, Donn F., 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 8)
    - Downing, Donn F. [RESTRICTED], 1964-1973 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Downs, Joan, 1976 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 9)
    - Drazgadze, Peter, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 10-12)
    - Dragadze, Peter [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Drozdiak, William, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 13)
    - Drozdiak, William [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Dubois, Larry, 1970 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 14)
    - DuBois, Larry [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Duffy, Martha, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 15)
    - Duncan, Richard (Dick), 1963-1967, 1977-1978, undated (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 16-17)
    - Duncan, Richard (Dick) [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Duncan, Richard (Dick): Memoranda, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 18-19)
    - Duncan, Richard (Dick): Personal, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 20-21)
    - Duncan, Richard (Dick): Personal: 1982 [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Duncan, Richard (Dick): Technology Speech, 1984 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 22)
    - Durham, Eileen, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 23)
    - Durham, Eileen [RESTRICTED], 1970-1973 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Durniak, John, 1977 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 24)
    - Eisendrath, Charles, 1969-1975 (Offsite-box 3210, Folder 25-26)
    - Eisendrath, Chares [RESTRICTED], 1968-1975 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Eisenstaedt, Alfred, 1945-1961 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 1)
    - Eisler, Kim, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 2)
    - Eisler, Kim [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Elegant, Robert, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 3)
    - Elia, Thomas, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 4)
    - Elia, Thomas [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Elliott, Lois, 1977, 1986 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 5)
    - Elliott, Lois [RESTRICTED], 1974-1986 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Ellis, Robert A., 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 6)
    - Elson, Robert, 1960-1973 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 7-8)
    - Elson, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R48)
    - English, Christopher, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 9)
    - English, Christopher [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Eschenbach, Waltraud, 1963-1976 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 10)
    - Eschenbach, Wally, 1969-1976 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 11-12)
    - Fagin, Jacqueline Lacroix, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 13)
    - Falkenhagen, Patricia, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 14)
    - Falkenhagen, Patricia [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Faulkner, Verrena [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Fayard, Judy, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 15)
    - Fayard, Judy [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Feldman, Kathleen B. [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Fentress, Simmons, 1961-1971, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 16-18)
    - Fentress, Simmons [RESTRICTED], 1964-1981 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Ferenbaugh, Dorothy, 1979-1986 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 19)
    - Ferenbaugh, Dorothy [RESTRICTED], 1978-1986 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Ferrera, Vincent [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Findlay, D.G.A., 1950 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 20)
    - Fischer, Dean, 1964-1983, undated (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 21-24)
    - Fischer, Dean [RESTRICTED], 1964-1983 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Fiorino, Frances, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 25)
    - Fiorino, Frances [RESTRICTED], 1980-1987 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Flamini, Roland, 1966-1983 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 26-28)
    - Flamini, Roland [RESTRICTED], 1969-1983 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Fodor, Denis, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 29)
    - Foltz, Charles, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 30)
    - Foote, Timothy, 1955-1958 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 31)
    - Forbath, T. Peter, 1962-1970 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 32-33)
    - Forbath, T. Peter [RESTRICTED], 1963-1971 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Forbis, William, 1949-1951, 1958, 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 3211, Folder 34-35)
    - Forbis, William [RESTRICTED], 1967-1969 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Forster, Georgina, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 1)
    - Forester, Georgina [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Fox, Barbara, 1970 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 2)
    - Fox, Barbara [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R48)
    - France, Alison [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Franks, Daniel [RESTRICTED], 1965, 1971-1987 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Frappollo, Liz, 1968-1976 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 3-4)
    - Frappollo, Liz [RESTRICTED], 1973-1977 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Friedman, William K., 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 5-6)
    - Friedman, William K. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Frook, John, 1964, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 7)
    - Froslid, Kenneth, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 8)
    - Fuerbringer, Otto, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 9)
    - Fuerbringer, Otto: Report on Europe: 1962 February (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 10)
    - Gallo, Jose, 1963-1971 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 11-12)
    - Garcia, Mo, 1961-1973 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 13)
    - Garcia, Mo [RESTRICTED], 1966-1970 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Garred, Eileen [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Gasner, Doug, 1969-1976 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 14)
    - Gasner, Doug [RESTRICTED], 1969-1972 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Geiger, Norbert, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 15)
    - Geline, Robert, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 16-17)
    - Geline, Bob [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Offsite-box R48)
    - George, Rosemary, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 18)
    - George, Rosemary [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Germano, Dianna, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 19)
    - Germano, Diana [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Getz, Michael, 1971 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 20)
    - Getz, Michael J. [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Ghosn, Najah, 1975 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 21)
    - Gillespie, Brooke, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 22)
    - Gillespie, Brooke [RESTRICTED], 1970-1975 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Gilliam, Gwen [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Gleason, Charles, 1965-1972 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 23)
    - Goldstein, Bob, 1973-1981 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 24)
    - Goldstein, Bob [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Goodale, Susan [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Gooding, Judson, 1957-1968 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 25)
    - Goodpaster, Ed, 1964-1972 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 26)
    - Goodpaster, Ed [RESTRICTED], 1964-1969 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Gordon, Leah, 1971-1972, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 27-28)
    - Gorey, Hays, 1964-1982 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 29-30)
    - Gorey, Hays [RESTRICTED], 1965-1982 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Gottfried, Manfred, 1945-1950, 1957, 1965 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 31)
    - Gottfried, Manfred: Bureau Project Files, 1958 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 32)
    - Grant, Zalin, 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 33)
    - Grant, Zalin [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Graves, Ralph, 1977-1986 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 34)
    - Green, Margaret [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Green, Martha McGahan, 1961-1976 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 34)
    - Greene, Florence [RESTRICTED], 1973-1980 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Greenway, David, 1963-1972 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 35-36)
    - Greenway, David [RESTRICTED], 1963-1972 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Griffith, Thomas, 1951-1961 (Offsite-box 3212, Folder 37)
    - Griffith, Thomas, 1962-1969 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 1)
    - Griggs, Lee, 1959-1985 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 2-5)
    - Griggs, Lee [RESTRICTED], 1978-1984 (Offsite-box R48)
    - Griggs, Lee [RESTRICTED], 1966-1982 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Grimaldi, Dolores, 1979 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 6)
    - Grimaldi, Dolores [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Gross, Karen M., 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 7)
    - Gross, Karen M. [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Grossman, Alan, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 8)
    - Grossman, Alan [RESTRICTED], 1966-1968 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Gruin, Fred, 1946-1949, 1955-1970 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 9-10)
    - Gruin, Fred [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Grum, Clifford, 1981 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 11)
    - Grunwald, Henry, 1951-1952, 1958-1987 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 12-14)
    - Grywalski, Terry, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 15)
    - Grywalski, Terry [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Guzzardi, Walter, 1955-1962 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 16-17)
    - Hagen, Leslie, 1972 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 18)
    - Hagen, Leslie [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hager, Barry M., 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 19)
    - Hager, Barry M. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hake, Susan, 1975-1979 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 20)
    - Hake, Susan [RESTRICTED], 1971-1979 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hall, Ted, 1972 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 21)
    - Hall, Ted [RESTRICTED], 1969-1973 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Halper, Sam, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 22-23)
    - Hamblin, Dodie, 1949-1961 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 24-25)
    - Harriss, Joe, 1963-1969 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 26)
    - Hathaway, Paul, 1966-1974 (Offsite-box 3213, Folder 27-28)
    - Hathaway, Paul [RESTRICTED], 1968-1973 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hauptfuhrer, Fred, 1969 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 1)
    - Haymaker, Martha, 1971-1979 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 2)
    - Haymaker, Martha, 1971, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Heiskell, Andrew, 1962-1972 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 3-5)
    - Henderson, Bruce, 1957-1961, 1978 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 6-9)
    - Henkel, Blanche, 1973 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 10)
    - Henkel, Blanche [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Herrman, Sabina (Beenie), 1973-1977 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 11)
    - Hill, Allan, 1979 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 12)
    - Hillenbrand, Barry, 1969-1983 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 13-15)
    - Hillenbrand, Barry [RESTRICTED], 1968-1982 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hodgson, Sue [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Holmes, Steven, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 16)
    - Holmes, Steven [RESTRICTED], 1979-1982 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hopkins, Verna [RESTRICTED], 1969-1972 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hornik, Richard, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 17)
    - Hornik, Richard [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Huff, Ken, 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 18)
    - Huff, Ken [RESTRICTED], 1970-1974 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hughes, Edward H., 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 19)
    - Hughes, Edward H. [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Hughes, Emmet, 1945-1960 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 20-22)
    - Hughes, Emmet J.: Personal and Confidential, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 23)
    - Jackson, David, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 24)
    - Jackson, David [RESTRICTED], 1978-1987 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Jones, Christopher, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 25)
    - Kane, Joseph, 1962-1982 (Offsite-box 3214, Folder 26-27)
    - Kane, Joseph [RESTRICTED], 1965-1982 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Larsen, Roy, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 1-2)
    - Leavitt, Russell, 1980-1987 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 3-4)
    - Linen, James, 1963-1968, 1975 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 5-6)
    - Linowitz, Sol, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 7)
    - Loeb, Marshall, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 8)
    - Luce, Clare Booth, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 9)
    - Luce, Clare Booth: Rome, 1967 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 10)
    - Luce, Henry III (Hank), 1965-1972 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 11)
    - Luce, Henry R., 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 12-13)
    - Luce, Henry R.: Condolances, 1967 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 14)
    - Mader, B. William (Bill), 1967-1982 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 15-18)
    - Mader, B. William (Bill) [RESTRICTED], 1966-1982 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Malkin, Lawrence (Larry), 1966-1986 (Offsite-box 3215, Folder 19-23)
    - Malkin, Lawrence (Larry) [RESTRICTED], 1973-1984 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Martin, Chuck, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 1)
    - McGeary. Johanna, 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 2)
    - McGeary, Johanna [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Offsite-box R49)
    - McWhirter, William, 1964-1984 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 3-7)
    - McWhirter, William [RESTRICTED], 1963, 1973-1982 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Minh, Le, 1980 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 8)
    - Moody, John, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 9-10)
    - Moody, John [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Nash, Madeleine, 1973-1982 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 11)
    - Nash, Madeleine [RESTRICTED], 1965, 1974-1983 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Nelan, Bruce, 1964-1983 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 12-14)
    - Nelan, Bruce [RESTRICTED], 1966-1983 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Nickel, Herman, 1958-1983 (Offsite-box 3216, Folder 15-17)
    - Nickel, Herman W. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1977 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Noble, Sara [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Offsite-box R49)
    - O'Connell. Rollande, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 1)
    - O'Connell, Rollande [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Ogden, Christopher, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 2)
    - Ogden, Christopher [RESTRICTED], 1974-1983 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Ogle, Ed, 1974 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 3)
    - Oltarzewski, Marlene, 1978 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 4)
    - O'Neil, Martin, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 5)
    - O'Neill, Pierre, 1972 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 6)
    - Orshefsky, Milton, 1953-1961 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 7)
    - Ostling, Richard, 1970-1975 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 8)
    - Ostling, Richard [RESTRICTED], 1971-1974 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Pace, Eric, 1961-1971 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 9)
    - Pace, Eric [RESTRICTED], 1964-1965 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Parker, Robert, 1960-1980 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 10)
    - Parker, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1965-1979 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Parks, Gordon, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 11)
    - Payne, Phil, 1951-1964 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 12)
    - Penchuk, Saralee [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Perry, William M., 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 13)
    - Pfister, Thomas M. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1973 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Phelps, Harold L. [RESTRICTED], 1971-1973 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Phillips, B.J., 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 14)
    - Phillips, B.J. [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Pigossi, Judith [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Pines, Burton: Yale, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 15)
    - Pines, Burton: Yale [RESTRICTED], 1969-1971 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Porterfield, Chris, 1963-1971 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 16)
    - Porterfield, Chris [RESTRICTED], 1963-1971 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Powell, Lee [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Praeger, Karsten, 1965-1983 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 17-18)
    - Praeger, Karsten [RESTRICTED], 1965-1968 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Prager, Karsten: Medicine [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Prendergast, Curtis W., 1950, 1957-1978 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 19)
    - Prendergast, Curtis W. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1978 (Offsite-box R49)
    - Prendergast, Sarah [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Price, Ruth Ann, 1975 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 20)
    - Purcell, John, 1946-1948, 1963 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 21)
    - Putnam, Conan [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Quirt, John, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 22)
    - Quirt, John [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Ramroth, Dorothea, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 23)
    - Range, Peter R., 1967-1976 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 24-25)
    - Range, Peter R. [RESTRICTED], 1969-1975 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Redman, Christopher, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 26)
    - Redman, Christopher [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Rehak, Peter, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 27)
    - Rehak, Peter [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Rein, Richard, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 28)
    - Rein, Richard [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Reingold, Edwin, 1969-1983 (Offsite-box 3217, Folder 29-30)
    - Reingold, Edwin, 1956-1973 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 1)
    - Reingold, Edwin [RESTRICTED], 1966-1983 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Ress, Paul, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 2)
    - Ress, Paul [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Rice, Delza [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Roche, Lee [RESTRICTED], 1972-1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Roe, David, 1970 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 3)
    - Rosenthal, Felix, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 4)
    - Rosenstein, Jay, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 5)
    - Rosenstein, Jay [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Roundtree, Ronnie Ray, 1971 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 6)
    - Roundtree, Ronnie Ray [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Rowan, Roy, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 7-8)
    - Rowan, Roy [RESTRICTED], 1970-1977 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Sachs, Art, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 9)
    - Saltonstall, Richard, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 10)
    - Saltonstall, Richard [RESTRICTED], 1965-1970 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Samghabadi, Raji, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 11-12)
    - Samghabadi, Raji [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Sanabria, Camille, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 13)
    - Sanabria, Camille [RESTRICTED], 1979-1982 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Sarkar, Prasanta, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 14)
    - Sasso, Francine [RESTRICTED], 1972-1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Saul, Jamie [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Schecter, Jerrold L. (Jerry), 1961-1977 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 15-21)
    - Schecter, Jerrold L. (Jerry) [RESTRICTED], 1963-1977 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Schenck, Holly [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Schlesinger, Stephen, 1974 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 22)
    - Schrobsdorff, Susanna [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Sciolino, Elaine, 1983 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 23)
    - Scott, Gavin, 1974-1983 (Offsite-box 3218, Folder 24-26)
    - Scott, Gavin, 1960-1982 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 1-2)
    - Scott, Gavin [RESTRICTED], 1970-1983 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Scott, John, 1975 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Johnie [RESTRICTED], 1972-1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Scott, Johnie, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 4)
    - Seaman, Barrett, 1976-1983 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 5)
    - Seaman, Barrett [RESTRICTED], 1977-1983 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Seddon, Mary Barbara, 1970-1972, 1978 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 6)
    - Seddon, Mary Barbara [RESTRICTED], 1969-1978 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Shaw, John, 1961-1977, 1985 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 7-11)
    - Shaw, John [RESTRICTED], 1965-1966, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Shaw, John Francis, 1970-1980 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 12)
    - Shaw, John Frances [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Shelton, William R., 1957-1968 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 13)
    - Shelton, William B. [RESTRICTED], 1957-1959 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Shenker, Israel, 1950-1965 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 14-16)
    - Shepherd, James, 1963-1978, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 17)
    - Shepherd, James [RESTRICTED], 1963, 1976 (Offsite-box R50)
    - Shepley, James, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 18)
    - Sherman, Gerd, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 3219, Folder 19)